{
    "id": "69180328ae5e4ae18d493347862bd141",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You ……………. not spit on the road. (Prohibition)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "will",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2fc8e3c1591d4bf4854289cf9024b05d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………. not steal. (Prohibition)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7cbb10d2bc9845bab105441702355c8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. behave herself. (Necessity)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "will",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32324f8ae5f54e449e595ecaee3e4e72"
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………. obey the rules. (Obligation)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "shall",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e2f40f77f26411998af62fdf82f8aaa"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you have finished your job, you ………………. go. (Permission)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "will",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "639cb834dd98480fa6939bf572114839"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. speak four languages. (Ability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e49b02b3950413db4c350ae0a03642a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………. read when she was just three years old. (Past ability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1fb3a7f45b3541e98ac9ebd96b3c6c85"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………….. stand on his head. (Ability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "will",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc1b15d56eb64500bef698e6d04972eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandmother is eighty. She ……………. still read without glasses. (Ability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "79571ff6404442d8b3f3e72cc0de3fc8"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I borrow your camera? (Permission)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Shall"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef8892f54b9945ee98487b0bdbff0498"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I’m starving.’ ‘I …………….. get you something to eat.’ (Willingness)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "767b7252fcbd4114b378c114d2dcdec9"
        }
    ]
}